(Raj:)Boy, all this standing's
making me tired.
(Raj:)Good thing I brought
my collapsible stick chair.
(Howard:)Not the stick chair.
(Howard:)You look like an idiot
on that thing.
(Raj:)Sticks and stones
may break my bones,
(Raj:)but chairs on sticks
are comfy.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hey.
(Sheldon:)Is everything
smoothed out with Amy?
(Stuart:)Uh, no, she's still pretty mad.
(Sheldon:)Did you make the apology
as sincere as I would have?
(Stuart:)I said,
“Sheldon says he's sorry.”
(Sheldon:)Oh, well, that's
laying it on a little thick.
(Leonard:)You think it's time you
apologize to her yourself?
(sighs)
I suppose so.
(Sheldon:)But if I get out of the line,
I'll lose my spot.
(Stuart:)I'm happy to hold your place
till you get back.
(Sheldon:)You would do that?
(Stuart:)Consider it my way
of getting more of your money.
(Sheldon:)You're a good man.
(Bernadette:)So, Beverly,
did you know Penny
(Bernadette:)is the number
three sales rep
(Bernadette:)at our pharmaceutical company?
(Beverly:)Oh, I didn't realize
you two work together.